exportmart.com 2012-10-27

# ExportMart.com, Privacy Policy, Registration,Publishing,Payment Mode, Users Policy,Business Norms

| 

This is the Privacy Policy governing your use of the Exportmart.com Site. 

By using this Site, you approve and agree to our Privacy Policy out below.

All terms are not defined in this document have the meanings ascribed to them in the Terms of Use Agreement between you and Exportmart.com which by use of this Site you agree to accept.

The fundamental purpose of the services that Exportmart.com provides you requires that we gather, process, use and distribute the member's information which also you provide directly by filling out our various forms and formats; for example, your company name, contact information, company profile and homepage and the products you buy and sell, etc. Therefore, Exportmart.com does not guarantee that your information will be protected from exposure in any particular party or group. 

1\. The Information We Collect 

**1.1** Registration Information. At the time you register to become a Registered User of the Site, you will be asked to fill out a registration form which requires you provide information such as your name, address, phone/fax number, email address and other personal information as well as information about your business.

**1.2** Publishing Information. If you submit any information to Exportmart.com to be published on the Site through the publishing tools, including but not limited to Company Directory, Product Catalog, Global Leads, then you are deemed to have given consent to the publication of such information. 

**1.3** Payment Information. If you establish a credit account with us or our providers or if you purchase a product or service from Exportmart.com or a vendor available through Exportmart.com, we collect additional information, including billing information, (but not credit card numbers and expiration dates) and tracking information from cheques or money orders. 

**1.4** Registration Information, Publishing Information, Payment Information, Statistical Information and any information we collect from you through the use of cookies or any other means shall collectively be referred to as "Collected Information". 

2\. How We Use Information 

**2.1** General. We use your Collected Information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our Site's content, layout and service specifically for you.

We use your Collected Information to service your Account with us, including but not limited to investigating problems, resolving disputes and enforcing agreements with us. We share certain aggregate information based on analysis of Collected Information with our partners, customers, advertisers or potential Users.

We use your Collected Information to execute marketing campaigns, promotions or advertising messages on behalf of third parties; however, in these circumstances, your Collected Information will not be disclosed to such third parties unless you respond to the marketing, promotion or advertising message.

**2.2** Registration Information. We use your Registration Information to provide services that you request or to contact you regarding additional services about which Exportmart.com determines that you might be interested.

Specifically, we use your email address, mailing address, phone number or fax number to contact you regarding notices, surveys, product alerts, new service or product offerings and communications relevant to your use of our Site, such as newsletters, if you choose to receive these as indicated at the time of registration.

We generate reports and analysis based on the Registration Information for internal analysis, monitoring and marketing decisions. 

**2.3** Publishing Information. Our Services are primarily designed to help connect traders with worldwide wholesalers, buyers, importers & exporters, manufacturers, suppliers and distributors in over 220 countries, quickly and cost effectively. Most of the information you are providing us is to make it public with your express consent. This includes not only the publishing of your company profile, contact details, banners, sell offers, buy offers, product displays, but also inquiries and messages you send to the Exportmart.com members using Exportmart.com services our amongst other services, which may be published on Exportmart.com website for your promotion.

By using the Exportmart.com services you are expressly and voluntarily accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and Exportmart.com User Agreement that allow Exportmart.com to process and publish your information, quiries and messages. Provision of information and messaging Exportmart.com members using Exportmart.com services, including any information deemed 'sensitive' by applicable law, is entirely voluntary on your part. 

You have the right to withdraw your consent to Exportmart.com collection, processing and publishing of your information at any time, in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy and the User Agreement, by unsubscribing your account, but please note that your withdrawal of consent will not be retroactive.Exportmart.com does not warrant how often third-party search engines will update their caches, which may exist in their archives, even after removing your provided information from Exportmart.com Your provided information is instantly published on our website and the same information may be searchable by many search engines and other means - you should be diligent about all information you provide Exportmart.com as the will not be liable for any unfavorable consequences arising out of the publishing of the provided information. Any Publishing Information that you disclose to Exportmart.com becomes public information.

**2.4** Payment Information. At Exportmart.com, your payment information will be collected by 3rd party vendor 'cc avenue.com' on its website http://www.ccavenue.com order to enable transactions to be completed by Exportmart.com. Any credit card information that you provide through the vendor Site is directly submitted to a payment server of the credit card processing bank. Ccavenue.com does not maintain electronic or physical copies of your credit card full information but just keep the 1st and last 4 digits of your credit card in order to validate the transaction.

The 'ccavenue.com' will not use the payment information collected for any secondary reasons, but only to perform and validate the transaction. While ccavenue.com has in place up-to-date technology and internal procedures to guard your Payment Information against intruders, there is no guarantee that such technology or procedure can eliminate all of the risks of theft, loss or mis-use. Exportmart.com shall not be liable to you or any other person for any damages that might result from unauthorized use, publication, disclosure or any other mis-use of Payment Information, including credit card information. 

**2.5** Statistical Information. We use Statistical Information to help diagnose problems with and maintain our computer servers, to manage our Site, and to enhance your Site and services based on the usage pattern data we receive.

We generate reports and analysis based on the Statistical Information for internal analysis, monitoring and marketing decisions.

We provide Statistical Information to third parties, but when we do so, we do not provide personally-identifying information without your permission. 

3\. Disclosure of Information

**3.1** We reserve the right to disclose your Collected Information to relevant authorities where we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who be infringing or threatening to infringe, or who otherwise be causing injury to or interference with, the title, rights, interests or property of Exportmart.com, our Users, customers, partners, other web site users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. 

**3.2** We also reserve the right to disclose Collected Information in response to a subpoena or other judicial order or when we reasonably believe that such disclosure is required by law, regulation or administrative order of any court, governmental or regulatory authority. 

**3.3** If we have reason to believe that a User is in breach of the Terms of User Agreement or any other agreement with us, then we reserve the right to make public or otherwise disclose such User's Collected Information in order to pursue our claim or prevent further injury to Exportmart.com or others. 

4\. Co-Branded Relationships 

Currently, Exportmart.com does not have any co-branding relationship with any other party.

5\. Cookies 

We use "cookies" to store specific information about you and track your visits to our Site. It is not uncommon for web sites to use cookies to enhance identification of their users. A "cookie" is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can be sent to your computer's hard drive only if you access our Site using the computer.

If you do not de-activate or erase the cookie, each time you use the same computer to access our Site, our web servers will be notified of your visit to our Site and in turn we have knowledge of your visit and the pattern of your usage.

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers, tracking utilities) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Exportmart.com at http://www.Exportmart.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties.

Generally, we use cookies to identify you and enable us to access your Registration Information, Publishing Information or Payment Information so you do not have to re-enter it; gather statistical information about usage by Users; research visiting patters and help target advertisements based on User interests; assist our partners to track User visits to the Site and process orders; and track progress and participation in promotions.

You can determine if and how a cookie will be accepted by configuring your browser's which is installed in the computer you are using to access the Site. If you desire, you can change those configurations in your browser.

By setting your preferences in the browser, you can accept all cookies, you can be notified when a cookie is sent, or you can reject all cookies. If you reject all cookies by choosing the cookie-disabling function in your browser, you be required to re-enter your information on our Site more often and certain features of our Site be unavailable. 

6\. Minors 

The Site and its contents are not intended to be targeted to minors under applicable law and we do not intend to sell any of our products or services to minors. However, we have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who access our Site and so we carry out the same Privacy Policy for individuals of all ages. If a minor has provided us with personal information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information. 

7\. Security Measures 

**7.1** We employ commercially reasonable security methods to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure correct use of information.

**7.2** As a Registered User, your Registration Information, Publishing Information and Payment Information (if any) can be viewed and edited through your Account which is protected by Password. We recommend that you do not divulge your Password to anyone.

Our personnel will never ask you for your Password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. If you share a computer with others, you should not choose to save your log-in information (e.g., User ID and Password) on the computer. Remember to sign out of your Account and close your browser window when you have finished your session.

**7.3** No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. As a result, while we try to protect your information, no web site or company, including ourselves, can absolutely ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. 

8\. Changes to Privacy Policy

Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be communicated through our posting an amended and restated Privacy Policy on our Site. Our posting the amended and restated Privacy Policy will make such new Privacy Policy immediately effective. 

You agree that all Collected Information (whether or not collected prior to or after the new policy became effective) will be governed by the newest Privacy Policy then in effect.

If you do not agree to the new changes in our Privacy Policy, you should contact Exportmart.com in writing (at the address set out in the Notice provision of the Terms of Use Agreement) and specifically request that Exportmart.com return and/or destroy all copies of all or part of your Collected Information in Exportmart.com's possession. 

9\. Correcting Your Information

You can access, view and edit your Registration Information, Publishing Information and Payment Information (if any) through your Account with Exportmart.com. To update or correct such information, unsubscribe to our email communications and/or de-list your company profile please send an email to info@Exportmart.com or by phone at +91120-4764800, or by visiting our website http://exportmart.com/contactus.aspx.

10\. Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact at:

Exportmart.com  
Mify Solutions Pvt.Ltd.  
Email: info@Exportmart.com
